<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Cloud Catcher Roastery - Specialty Coffee Roaster]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Cloud Catcher Roastery - Specialty Coffee Roaster]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/cloud-catcher/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 04:51:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/cloud-catcher/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let’s Get Serious About Coffee]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Let’s Get Serious About Coffee</h1><p>At Cloud Catcher, we are excited to share with you what we have learned about the coffee trade and craft. If you’re a serious coffee lover looking to start your own café or simply a curious coffee addict who wants to learn more about coffee, we invite you to come on a coffee journey with us and experience a holistic and intensive education that begin in May 2016 at our brand new state-of-the-art facility in Jalan 225, Petaling Jaya. We also look forward to taking you on farm tours to show you how coffee is cultivated at its origin.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/fa5f757faf787fa9f9b7c24df94b8f0548cecc52.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/cloud-catcher/at-cloud-catcher-we-are-excited-to-share-with-you-what-we-h/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7b0bf8ec-50d0-487e-a6d4-5013420fe76e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 04:51:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Coffee Journey]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Our Coffee Journey</h1><p>The understanding of how good coffee is made is a long, tedious, continuous but fun process. Cloud Catcher started from scratch by tracing the green beans back to its origins and learning how they are treated as young saplings in the nursery, choosing the right soil, harvesting, sorting, blending, roasting, cupping and scoring based on taste. Every step in the production of a good of coffee is interrelated, you need good brewing skills, an exceptional roast profile and, of course, un-compromised farming techniques at the source (soil, climate, selective picking, processing, etc)</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/cloud-catcher/the-understanding-of-how-good-coffee-is-made-is-a-long-tedi/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e53cd1f8-9dc7-43d5-adba-7bf9f59e0792</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 04:48:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Give Back]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We Give Back</h1><p>Sustainable relationships with the farmers is the foundation of our philosophy. This means helping them improve their crop to ensure quality coffee is produced consistently, keeping them in business. Responsible sourcing, the environment, quality, and you, the customer, come first which is why we take pride and care in ensuring that every green bean is bought directly from quality committed farmers at a more than fair rate via Project Origin & Chapola Project. The farmers we do business with are well compensated above market standards so that every green bean produced is grown with love and all our coffees taste exquisite.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/cloud-catcher/sustainable-relationships-with-the-farmers-is-the-foundation/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1df86676-6324-48f1-a632-fcd88faf02a9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 04:43:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Travel]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>We Travel</h1><p>Cloud Catcher is Asia's one-stop centres for specialty coffee based in Malaysia.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/cloud-catcher/cloud-catcher-is-asias-one-stop-centres-for-specialty-coffe/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a095c199-e892-4e27-ba40-31608d8ce6bc</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 04:38:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>